questionsThree = [
    {
      "Question":"1. An instruction or command sentence in a programming language\n that will be executed by the computer is called?",
      "choices": [
               "Statement",
               "Syntaks",
               "Program",
               "Scratch",
      ],
      "Answer": "Statement",
    },
    {
        "Question":"2. The set of rules in a programming language that defines the combination \n of symbols that are considered a properly structured document is called?",
        "choices": [
                "Statement",
                "Syntaks",
                "Program",
                "Scratch",
        ],
        "Answer": "Syntaks",
    },
    {
        "Question":"3. What is the purpose of the __str__ method in Python?",
        "choices": [
                "Convert an object to a string",
                "Define the class constructor",
                "Access the attributes of an object",
                "Raise an exception when the object is not found",
        ],
        "Answer": "Convert an object to a string",
    },
    {
        "Question":"4. How can you open a file named 'example.txt' in Python \n for both reading and writing?",
        "choices": [
                'file = open("example.txt", "r+w")',
                'file = open("example.txt", "rw")',
                'file = open("example.txt", "r+")',
                'file = open("example.txt", "w+")',
        ],
        "Answer": 'file = open("example.txt", "r+")',
    },
    {
        "Question":"5. In Python, what is the purpose of the __enter__ and __exit__ \n methods in the context manager protocol?",
        "choices": [
                'Initialize and finalize an object',
                'Enter and exit a code block with resource management',
                'Access and modify class attributes',
                'Create and destroy instances of a class',
        ],
        "Answer": 'Enter and exit a code block with resource management',
    },
    {
        "Question":"6. What does the *args syntax in a function definition represent in Python?",
        "choices": [
                'Keyword arguments',
                'Default arguments',
                'variable-length arguments',
                'Named arguments',
        ],
        "Answer": 'Variable-length arguments',
    },
    {
        "Question":"7. What is the purpose of the functools.partial function in Python?",
        "choices": [
                'Create a partially applied function',
                'Define default values for function parameters',
                'Extend the functionality of built-in functions',
                'Decorate a function with additional behavior',
        ],
        "Answer": 'Create a partially applied function',
    },
    {
        "Question":"8. What is the key difference between sets and frozensets in Python?",
        "choices": [
                'Sets are mutable, while frozensets are immutable',
                'Sets allow duplicate elements, while frozensets do not',
                'Sets support indexing, while frozensets do not',
                'Sets can only contain numeric elements, \n while frozensets can contain any data type',
        ],
        "Answer": 'Sets are mutable, while frozensets are immutable',
    },
    {
        "Question":"9. In Python, what does the __name__ attribute represent when used in a script?",
        "choices": [
                'The name of the module',
                'The name of the function',
                'The name of the class',
                'The name of the script',
        ],
        "Answer": 'The name of the script',
    },
    {
        "Question":"10. Which of the following statements is true regarding Python's zip() function?",
        "choices": [
                'zip() creates a deep copy of the given iterable.',
                'zip() combines multiple iterables element-wise into tuples.',
                'zip() is used for compressing files in Python.',
                'zip() can only be applied to lists.',
        ],
        "Answer": 'zip() combines multiple iterables element-wise into tuples.',
    },
]